<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on 热港 | Vesuvius Harbor</title>
        <link>https://heartoftheearth.dk/post/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on 热港 | Vesuvius Harbor</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>Stella</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:08:50 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://heartoftheearth.dk/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>20231015</title>
        <link>https://heartoftheearth.dk/p/20231015/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:08:50 +0200</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://heartoftheearth.dk/p/20231015/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Spring, a humpback whale lands in my hometown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Stranded&amp;rdquo;—here, people are more accustomed to calling it that,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a dying fishing boat, slashing towards the billions of tons of yellow sand, a full stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(A low-probability event! The news is conclusive.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As heavy as lightning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What once pierced my youthful heart was the narrow lens, from autumn waters,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;swooping towards the Northern Sea, swelling with the vast and silent wings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, the weary misnavigation,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I studied, biology, geography, history, war, tracing back to all&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;races—my presumed race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reasons for parting ways, and it never needs to learn again,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;five hundred and forty million years ago, a mother tongue named &amp;ldquo;breath.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The tide&amp;hellip; comes at eleven at night&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chronic death notice repeats on the dining table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pouring the heads of warm cold currents and monsoons, you are in the process of&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;romanticizing the swiftly decaying selective forgetting, the waxing crescent moon has not yet cut open&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a bright sea surface, and daylight has already equated to the extinction of dreams.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>23 丰实月｜月末小结</title>
        <link>https://heartoftheearth.dk/p/23-%E4%B8%B0%E5%AE%9E%E6%9C%88%E6%9C%88%E6%9C%AB%E5%B0%8F%E7%BB%93/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 13:56:27 +0200</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://heartoftheearth.dk/p/23-%E4%B8%B0%E5%AE%9E%E6%9C%88%E6%9C%88%E6%9C%AB%E5%B0%8F%E7%BB%93/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://heartoftheearth.dk/img/20231001.jpg" alt="Featured image of post 23 丰实月｜月末小结" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;01/10  The sea is bright, overcast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m in my sixth week in Copenhagen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My love for this city has not faded. My favorite is the Norreport metro station in the city center, where people often perform by the fountain. When it rains, the music travels through the rain lines, clear and melodious, like flowing creamy silk. The nearby flower shop&amp;rsquo;s peonies are too expensive, but they used to sell small strawberries for ten kroner a box, very sweet. I also like the little red trains here, called S-tog. When I first arrived, I took the wrong direction and got off at an unfamiliar platform, on a hillside. The towns below looked like miniature scenes in a crystal ball, with abundant clouds. Under the clear blue sky, everything shone in metallic colors, clean and beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In terms of academics, the workload is probably not as heavy as the rumors about students studying in Germany, the Netherlands, or Belgium. However, handling one BSA exam requires effort in organizing thoughts for the oral test. Additionally, my English listening and speaking skills are weaker compared to local European students, so there&amp;rsquo;s no shortcut; I have to take it step by step. MLA is more theoretical than I imagined. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if that&amp;rsquo;s good or bad, but it has some advantages. The assignments provide me with opportunities to speak in front of other international students, a kind of unpretentious &amp;ldquo;self-exposure,&amp;rdquo; and I&amp;rsquo;m becoming more proficient in writing LaTeX articles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last week, I skipped class and attended a career counseling session, where I learned about some cultural differences. They value personal &amp;ldquo;soft skills&amp;rdquo; more in this place, but I still need to carefully edit and enhance my CV, LinkedIn, and similar things. I feel like time is running out, but procrastination is not an option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, there&amp;rsquo;s a pile of miscellaneous tasks, starting from my arrival: getting a transportation card, opening a bank account, buying a bicycle, scheduling a doctor&amp;rsquo;s appointment, arranging rent payments, online shopping, and so on. All of these require continuous communication to accomplish. But I finally have more control over my life, which is considered progress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This semester, academics weigh heavily, but I&amp;rsquo;ve always been eager to improve my social skills. I&amp;rsquo;m still considering volunteering or finding a part-time job to practice my English. There are many friendly people I&amp;rsquo;ve met, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to start a conversation, which is truly distressing. After these two courses end, I&amp;rsquo;ll email a professor outside the university to inquire about the possibility of working in their lab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also decided to dedicate at least half an hour every day to exercise. The lower back is a fragile part of the human body, and yet I can&amp;rsquo;t avoid long periods of sitting. I randomly signed up for a K-pop dance course at school. Taming my limbs is quite challenging, but since I&amp;rsquo;ve already paid, I might as well continue. I remember going to the doctor about half a month ago, and he said I&amp;rsquo;m still very young. I was quite dazed at the time. He believes this age marks the beginning of a great life, so I&amp;rsquo;ll take it as such.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve made progress in cooking, and standing in the kitchen away from electronic screens is not a bad thing. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to try bringing lunch to school three days a week, but I despise the thought of washing pots and dishes. I&amp;rsquo;m considering buying a new air fryer this month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went to a friend&amp;rsquo;s house for dinner, which was the first time meeting an online friend. I was very happy. I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to &amp;ldquo;take the relationship a step further&amp;rdquo; for a long time. Even in cp29, I didn&amp;rsquo;t really meet and interact with each other. But sometimes, I sincerely hope for a good outcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, I regret that after October, there was a lot of wind and rain, and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go hiking in early autumn or read some leisure books. Mid-Autumn Festival passed by in a daze, and there&amp;rsquo;s still so much to do. During the autumn break, I still plan to visit the Louisiana Museum, and there&amp;rsquo;s no rush to revisit New Carlsberg. I want to explore other places too, and getting a youth card is essential for this. I wonder if I can go whale-watching in Norway after the semester ends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;October, in the Kunya language, is called Narquelië, the month of fading sun, the nights lengthen and the days shorten after the autumnal equinox. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to dress warmly.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
